<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Malware Analysis - ANY.RUN's Cybersecurity Blog</title><link /><description>Cybersecurity Blog covers topics for experienced professionals as well as for those new to it.</description><item><title>Salty 2FA: Undetected PhaaS from Storm-1575 Hitting US and EU Industries</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/salty2fa-technical-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, phishing accounts for the majority of all cyberattacks. The availability of low-cost, easy-to-use Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platforms like Tycoon2FA, EvilProxy, and Sneaky2FA only makes the problem worse.&amp;#160; These services are actively maintained by their operators; new evasion techniques are regularly added, and the multi-layered infrastructure behind the phishing kits continues to evolve and expand.&amp;#160; But [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/salty2fa-technical-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Salty 2FA: Undetected PhaaS from Storm-1575 Hitting US and EU Industries &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:32:41 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category><category>malware behavior</category></item><item><title>PyLangGhost RAT: Rising Stealer from Lazarus Group Striking Finance and Technology</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/pylangghost-malware-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Editor’s note:&amp;#160;The current article is authored by Mauro Eldritch, offensive security expert and threat intelligence analyst. You can&amp;#160;find Mauro on X.&amp;#160; North Korean state-sponsored groups, such as Lazarus, continue to target the financial and cryptocurrency sectors with a variety of custom malware families. In previous research, we examined strains like InvisibleFerret, Beavertail, and OtterCookie, often [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/pylangghost-malware-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;PyLangGhost RAT: Rising Stealer from Lazarus Group Striking Finance and Technology &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>guest post</category><category>malware analysis</category></item><item><title>Major Cyber Attacks in July 2025: Obfuscated .LNK‑Delivered DeerStealer, Fake 7‑Zip, and More</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/cyber-attacks-july-2025/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;While cybercriminals were working overtime this July, so were we at ANY.RUN — and, dare we say, with better results. As always, we’ve picked the most dangerous and intriguing attacks of the month. But this time, there’s more.&amp;#160; Alongside the monthly top, we are highlighting a key trend that’s been powering campaigns throughout 2025: the [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/cyber-attacks-july-2025/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Major Cyber Attacks in July 2025: Obfuscated .LNK‑Delivered DeerStealer, Fake 7‑Zip, and More&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category><category>malware behavior</category></item><item><title>Beating Supply Chain Attacks: DHL Impersonation Case Study</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/supply-chain-attacks-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;ANY.RUN’s services processes data on current threats daily, including attacks affecting supply chains. In this case study, we analyze examples of DHL brand abuse. The company is a leading global logistic operator, and attackers exploit its recognition to send phishing emails, potentially targeting its partners.&amp;#160;&amp;#160; We will demonstrate how ANY.RUN’s solutions can be used to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/supply-chain-attacks-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Beating Supply Chain Attacks: DHL Impersonation Case Study  &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:50:54 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category></item><item><title>Technical Analysis of Ducex: Packer of Triada Android Malware</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/ducex-packer-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Many have probably heard of the modular malware for mobile devices called Triada. Even nine years after its first mention in 2016, it remains one of the most advanced Android trojans out there. Recently, our team at ANY.RUN came across an interesting sample of this malicious software. The sample in question was embedded in a [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/ducex-packer-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Technical Analysis of Ducex: Packer of Triada Android Malware &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:42:38 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category></item><item><title>DEVMAN Ransomware: Analysis of New DragonForce Variant</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/devman-ransomware-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Editor’s note: The current article is authored by Mauro Eldritch, offensive security expert and threat intelligence analyst. You can find Mauro on X.&amp;#160; New ransomware strains continue to surface frequently, and many of them are loosely built on or repackaged from existing families. One such case involves a sample resembling DragonForce ransomware, yet bearing several [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/devman-ransomware-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;DEVMAN Ransomware: Analysis of New DragonForce Variant &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 09:47:55 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category></item><item><title>Top 3 Cyber Attacks in June 2025: GitHub Abuse, Control Flow Flattening, and More</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/cyber-attacks-june-2025/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;June 2025 saw several sophisticated and stealthy cyber attacks that relied heavily on obfuscated scripts, abuse of legitimate services, and multi-stage delivery techniques. Among the key threats observed by ANY.RUN’s analysts were malware campaigns using GitHub for payload hosting, JavaScript employing control-flow flattening to drop Remcos, and obfuscated BAT scripts delivering NetSupport RAT. Let’s see [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/cyber-attacks-june-2025/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Top 3 Cyber Attacks in June 2025: GitHub Abuse, Control Flow Flattening, and More &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:47:26 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware analysis</category></item><item><title>Cyber Attacks on Government Agencies: Detect and Investigate with ANY.RUN for Fast Response</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/how-to-investigate-government-cyber-attacks/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Government institutions worldwide face a growing number of sophisticated cyberattacks. This case study examines how ANY.RUN’s solutions can be leveraged to detect, analyze, and mitigate cyber threats targeting government organizations.&amp;#160; By analyzing real-world threats, we demonstrate how ANY.RUN’s Threat Intelligence Lookup, Interactive Sandbox, and YARA Search assist cybersecurity teams in identifying attack vectors, tracking malicious [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/how-to-investigate-government-cyber-attacks/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Cyber Attacks on Government Agencies: Detect and Investigate with ANY.RUN for Fast Response&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware</category><category>malware analysis</category><category>malware behavior</category></item><item><title>OtterCookie: Analysis of Lazarus Group Malware Targeting Finance and Tech Professionals</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/ottercookie-malware-analysis/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Editor’s note:&amp;#160;The current article is authored by Mauro Eldritch, offensive security expert and threat intelligence analyst. You can&amp;#160;find Mauro on X.&amp;#160; What looks like a simple freelance bug fix turns out to be a full-blown malware infection. OtterCookie, a new tool from the Lazarus Group APT, hides behind clean code and fake job offers, then [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/ottercookie-malware-analysis/" rel="nofollow"&gt;OtterCookie: Analysis of Lazarus Group Malware Targeting Finance and Tech Professionals&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:25:08 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>cybersecurity</category><category>malware</category><category>malware analysis</category><category>malware behavior</category></item><item><title>How MSSPs Can Analyze and Investigate Phishing Attacks with ANY.RUN</title><link>https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/how-to-investigate-phishing-attacks/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Phishing attacks have become a pervasive and escalating threat across various industries, notably in finance, manufacturing, and healthcare. For Managed Security Service Providers (MSSPs), the challenge lies in swiftly identifying and mitigating these threats to safeguard client infrastructures and uphold service integrity.&amp;#160; This case study explores how ANY.RUN’s Threat Intelligence Lookup and Interactive Sandbox can [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog/how-to-investigate-phishing-attacks/" rel="nofollow"&gt;How MSSPs Can Analyze and Investigate Phishing Attacks with ANY.RUN &lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://any.run/cybersecurity-blog" rel="nofollow"&gt;ANY.RUN&amp;#039;s Cybersecurity Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate><category>Malware Analysis</category><category>ANYRUN</category><category>malware analysis</category><category>malware behavior</category></item></channel></rss>